{
  "type": "audio2hira",
  "level": "SEION",
  "questions": [
    { "prompt": "あ", "answer": "あ" },
    { "prompt": "い", "answer": "い" },
    { "prompt": "う", "answer": "う" },
    { "prompt": "え", "answer": "え" },
    { "prompt": "お", "answer": "お" },
    { "prompt": "か", "answer": "か" },
    { "prompt": "き", "answer": "き" },
    { "prompt": "く", "answer": "く" },
    { "prompt": "け", "answer": "け" },
    { "prompt": "こ", "answer": "こ" },
    { "prompt": "さ", "answer": "さ" },
    { "prompt": "し", "answer": "し" },
    { "prompt": "す", "answer": "す" },
    { "prompt": "せ", "answer": "せ" },
    { "prompt": "そ", "answer": "そ" },
    { "prompt": "た", "answer": "た" },
    { "prompt": "ち", "answer": "ち" },
    { "prompt": "つ", "answer": "つ" },
    { "prompt": "て", "answer": "て" },
    { "prompt": "と", "answer": "と" },
    { "prompt": "な", "answer": "な" },
    { "prompt": "に", "answer": "に" },
    { "prompt": "ぬ", "answer": "ぬ" },
    { "prompt": "ね", "answer": "ね" },
    { "prompt": "の", "answer": "の" },
    { "prompt": "は", "answer": "は" },
    { "prompt": "ひ", "answer": "ひ" },
    { "prompt": "ふ", "answer": "ふ" },
    { "prompt": "へ", "answer": "へ" },
    { "prompt": "ほ", "answer": "ほ" },
    { "prompt": "ま", "answer": "ま" },
    { "prompt": "み", "answer": "み" },
    { "prompt": "む", "answer": "む" },
    { "prompt": "め", "answer": "め" },
    { "prompt": "も", "answer": "も" },
    { "prompt": "や", "answer": "や" },
    { "prompt": "ゆ", "answer": "ゆ" },
    { "prompt": "よ", "answer": "よ" },
    { "prompt": "ら", "answer": "ら" },
    { "prompt": "り", "answer": "り" },
    { "prompt": "る", "answer": "る" },
    { "prompt": "れ", "answer": "れ" },
    { "prompt": "ろ", "answer": "ろ" },
    { "prompt": "わ", "answer": "わ" },
    { "prompt": "を", "answer": "を" },
    { "prompt": "ん", "answer": "ん" }
  ]
}
